Hi everyone! Welcome to another video here on my channel. It's the first video I'm recording since I took a small break from YouTube and I'm so excited to do this one because I've been obsessing over these products for a month and I'm really happy to be able to show them to you.
Today I'm going to show you leather harness sets together with cool mesh bodysuits from Marie Mour.
And they do make great products and the packaging is already great.
So all of them came in these nice boxes.
If you open them, there was a bag inside.
so hint for all the guys there it's a great idea for gift and you don't even
have to wrap it yourself you know what I mean
so first that I'm going to show you is
Hello!
And let me get everything out here.
It's real leather and the set contains a chest piece, a hip and leg piece which is totally untangled now.
And two cuffs.
And there is a bodysuit matching to this one somewhere.
This is the bag I put all the bodysuits in.
Yeah, it's this one.
So this is the bodysuit, which is a great match for the colour and really see through.
So you have to kind of decide what you want to wear underneath, if you want to wear something
underneath.
And then put the harnesses on top of it.
The calves come with two, I don't know, bridge pieces so to say.
you can clip that in everywhere like here in the leg harness or even in the chest piece.
By the way this one makes a great booty and it looks really good from behind.
Totally confused with all the straps here.
and the chest piece also has really thick leather strips so it is really
high quality all this what I'm showing you here and I do have a promotion code
if you want to order to use my name silly knocks for 15% discount code and
of course you will find a discount code and all the links of all the stuff I'm
showing to you in the description text beneath this video. Have a look there.
I'm going to show you four sets today. Two black ones, this blue one and a pink one.
So they have a great range of colors as well which I like because normally all the
harnesses you find online are just black and I think this is a nice change with these
cool colors. I think I'll have to hang them for storing. That's also what is
suggested. So let's do black one next. For the black harness I ordered a blue body
suit because I was like a black bodysuit is maybe too boring for the black
harnesses. I love the cut of this one with the crisscross in the front here.
and the black edges here on the blue mesh really really nice
and now, oh god this is a big piece, this is the hip piece
let me check if it's this way around
so for your stomach and hips and the legs
And there is a second piece in this set for the chest and your neck.
So this is super adjustable. You have snaps here which you can reattach and attach if you don't want to use the leg things here.
Then just remove them. And you can adjust everything because there are a lot of holes you can use.
What I also love is that if you adjust the straps and you have such a long piece hanging
around here you can hide it because there are a lot of loops here which you can put
it through so it's not loose anymore and not hanging around somewhere.
Also the bunch of wood is quite heavy because there are a lot of metal parts processed here
which kind of looks really cool and I think this harness together with the bodysuit looks really
badass I think the most badass from all of the harnesses here for the third outfit is like
this surprise color it's pink and all the metal parts are gold in here so it is such a nice
combination and I have to say it works so well with my hair still love my hair sorry not sorry
for bleaching them and putting blue paint on them. Anyway this is the leg and hip part.
We have two cuffs which is so cute because what I like about them is that they criss-cross
here in the middle, the straps. Really cool feature, really cool design feature. And the
chest piece with an integrated collar and I love these huge golden rings here
they're so cool. And for this one I have a bodysuit as well which is pink as well.
You probably know me by now I'm not the biggest fan of pink I prefer black but I
took pictures of this set yesterday in the evening and it looked so cool
together and I was like wow okay I wouldn't have expected that also it has the same cut than blue
bodysuit here but it is like color in color with only pink colors here and looks super cute with
set here I'm not a fan of pink but I have to admit it's so cute I saw it was like me okay
hair. Also with the hair. I have to stress out the hair again. I think this is my... I don't know if
it is my favorite, but it is one of my two favorite sets, which I wouldn't have expected at all.
There are two golden carabiners. Carabiners? Carabiners? Carabiners. There are two golden
carabiners like this set, which means you can also attach the cuffs to the waist belt again
and use it for the things you like.
This is the last set. It's black again and it is a bit different from the other ones. There are
one, two, three, four, five pieces in the set but
nothing for the neck.
So these are for the thighs.
And for the arms.
And more brutal work for the waist.
On which you can attach the thigh belts here of course.
And there are keys for this set because it's closed with locks.
Where is the lock?
Here are the locks.
Or here are the locks.
And on every piece there is at least one lock.
If you're worrying about losing the keys, don't worry, there are one, two, three, four spare keys here.
But of course you should keep them safe somewhere.
And what I really love is that there is an imprint of the Marie Moulle logo here in the leather.
I can really recommend this one.
All of these, because they feel really nice to the touch.
and you can kind of really feel that this is some quality work. Also the edges here are really
smooth. It's not just cut away but you have round edges for example and also all the snaps and all
the metal parts are really smooth and feel really nice. I really have to say thank you to Marimoo
for approaching me and asking me if I want to collaborate with them. I love your products.
I'm totally hyped. I'm really excited that I'm able to present him. Oh, by the way, I combined
this one again with the blue bodysuit here. These are like the Marie Moua outfits. They're sold
together partially and they do combine a lot of the leather stuff with mesh bodysuits. But I can't
think of so many other cool combinations and outfits which I can style with these accessories.
so I'm pretty sure I'll do another video and show you some alternative styling ideas with all the
harder sets here. I hope you had fun with this video. I had a lot of fun presenting all of these
and showing them to you. I wish you a great day. Hit the subscribe button if you liked this video
and see you at the next one. Bye!